{
  "quiz": [
    {
      "question": "Assisttive mode not working properly, patient not able to reach flags?",
      "answer": "Done callibration at customer place, given complete training about MMT"
    },
    {
      "question": "Bluetooth connection isssue?",
      "answer": "Ardino Replaced"
    },
    {
      "question": "How can users edit a patient's profile?",
      "answer": "Users can edit a patient's profile through the provided interface for editing patient profiles."
    },
    {
      "question": "Removed locking knob of tablet stand?",
      "answer": "Sent video for fixing the knob"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tab Locked. need to foramat & APPs need to reinstall?",
      "answer": "Given online support for app installation & Calibration"
    },
    {
      "question": "Knee hip attachment not fixing properly?",
      "answer": "Replaced Knee-Hip Attachment Brace & Adaptor"
    },
    {
      "question": "App Not working?",
      "answer": "Software upgradation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Knee hip attachment not fixing properly?",
      "answer": "Replaced Knee-Hip Attachment Brace & Adaptor"
    },
    {
      "question": "Grub screw loosen?",
      "answer": "Given online instructions"
    }, 
    {
      "question": "Not feeling assitance and resistance?",
      "answer": "Check emergancy switch and it should not press"
    },
    {
      "question": "Training mode not working properly ?",
      "answer": "Restart the application or Restart the tab"
    },
    {
      "question": "Bluetooth connection isssue ?",
      "answer": "Restart the application or Restart the tab"
    },
    {
      "question": "Human effort not showing ?",
      "answer": "switch on the machine without attaching the attachment"
    },

    {
      "question": "Patient not able to reach target ?",
      "answer": "Check the fulcrum position match with respect to joint"
    },
    {
      "question": "Noise from the machine ?",
      "answer": "Reduse the range"
    },

    {
      "question": "Not able to fix attachment ?",
      "answer": "Contact to service center"
    },

    {
      "question": "Machine not switch on ?",
      "answer": "Check the power cable or Contact to service center"
    },
    {
      "question": "In ADL application movement in wrong direction ?",
      "answer": "Switch side position"
    }
  ]
}